Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout was headed for the royal capital.
Oh boy, I think it's finally time for me to have some fun for real!
Overcome by rage and a thirst for revenge, the elf possessing Lux's body unleashed a ruthless attack in a crowded town, poised to kill every human in sight.
This ain't right. I was expecting to run into a bad guy here. Instead we find you. Why?
The change in Lux's behavior was a shock to Vanessa and Magna, but they engaged him in battle nonetheless.
Flame magic! Gargantuan exploding pharaoh!
You're nothing but an imposter. And that means you don't know the first thing about him or about me. So come at me all you want, but you'll never win.
Now give our squad mate back to us, right now!
But everything they did only seemed to increase his resistance.
Now every human in this kingdom will die. That's the fate you deserve and we elves will be happy to make it a reality.
Magna was inches away from death until...
You think I'd let you hurt them?
Not a chance!
And who are you?
We're Lux's friends and fellow magic knights!
With us...
We asked...
Tell me...
Feel right, for the purpose of life,
Staying with us...
Listen up!
Tell me or I'm not except you could
Let's!
止まんない衝動
どんでもなれ
やんぬいがいないんでしょ?
分かり合えない場所を
やり切るまで
染められる風の世界
生きる全てが来なるまでやるよ
Let's!
Drawing!
Found him!
And he's headed straight for me!
He can't escape now!
My rage overpowers everything!
There you are!
He messed up my timing!
Now!
He's wide open!
You're strong but our bond is stronger!
You lose!
Nice going Asa!
Now let's get you out of there!
You humans are doomed!
Just wait and see!
You really don't know when to throw in the towel!
Do ya punk?
You're not going to give up on our friend!
We told you!
Stop it!
Get your hands on me!
That's weird!
Someone's voice!
I could just barely make it out and now it's gone!
Wink up!
Luck!
If that pisses you off!
Then snap out of it!
And fight me already you little moron!
The red thread of fate has you!
Take control of your body and stop this!
What's going on?
Who is that?
Luck?
Mom!
The red thread of fate has you!
Take control of your body and stop this!
What's going on?
Who is that?
Luck?
Mom!
Come to my side my son!
You're not like everyone else!
You have to stay close to me!
That's right!
The only person who could ever love me is my mother!
She's my life!
Everything I do is for her!
All I want to do is make her smile!
I'm gonna use all of my magic!
Then everything will be destroyed!
You,the rest of these humans and even me!
I want all of you revolting humans to disappear for good!
What's going on with his keys?
Is this really magic?
I can sense something dark and sinister welling up!
Hey!
This ain't over!
It's just like that guy!
At this rate, he's gonna turn into something that's not an elf at all!
Something that's actually evil!
You took them all!
Everyone who was precious to me!
You killed them!
That's why!
I swear I'll make you pay!
I don't know what you're talking about!
But if humans are to blame for what happened,I'm sorry!
I really mean it!
But look!
He's precious to us!
We're friends!
And we wouldn't ever want to lose him!
So please!
Don't take him away!
That's right!
Let go of him before it's too late!
I'm sure the people you cared about wouldn't want you to make someone else go through that same pain you did back then!
Get out!
Mom!
Look!
Look!Look!Look!
Look!Look!
Those voices!
I'm sorry mom!
But I have to go now!
Okay!
I found people who like me the way I am!
So goodbye!
And thank you for everything!
Starting today you'll be a member of the Black Bulls!
Go as crazy as you want!
You little boy!
Good ass.
Good ass!
Starting to day you'll be a member of the Black Bulls!
Go as crazy as you want you little brat!
What's going on there new guy?
Awwwww Look at you,you're adorable!
From now on you can think of me as your big sister okay?
Aww, look at you. You're adorable! From now on, you can think of me as your big sister, okay?
It's a pleasure to make your appointments, my new wife.
Have a bite of this?! Go on!
This is my sister Marie. Yes, I know. She's a goddess. You can worship her all you like.
I don't care what you think about me. Think whatever you want. But just so you know, I'm gonna think of you as my friend. No, wait, he's our friend!
I can't believe you're technically my superior, but since I'm royalty, I'll overlook it.
The final isn't gonna be between you and that Yuno guy. It's between me and Luck!
I do, too.
I truly believe there will soon come a day when all of us can exist together in harmony. Let's foster understanding.
Humans. Elves. I wanted to become friends with your kind. I really believed that I could.
I really believed that I could.
The final is.
Huh.
Hello.
It's been a long 이런 welield.
Um, guys, tell me, can I still be in the black balls?
What are you talking about, kid?
Of course you can.
Magna!
Vanessa!
Asta!
Thanks a lot!
Come on!
He can tell you to back off all he wants, but he's happier than anyone that you're okay!
We saw him hugging you, it was adorable!
Yeah, embrace your feelings, Magna!
The only thing you're gonna be feeling is my foot across your face, you pug!
Aw, look, you're so embarrassed!
Like hell I am!
Be mature about it!
Says the brat!
But seriously, thank you guys.
Oh, I guess I messed up the town.
I wouldn't really call that news, you little force of nature.
I hope none of the residents got injured.
I made sure they were all safe.
No need to fret.
That's good, thank you so much, Vanessa!
Uh, don't I deserve some credit?
Yeah, I guess.
What the hell do you mean, yeah, I guess?
Explosives got down!
Aw, crap, I'm out of juice.
And you!
Asta!
What did I do?
What's with the sword?
Huh?
This thing?
It turned luck back to normal.
The way Yuno put it, it takes somebody's magic and sucks it out, I guess?
So basically it's like the spell was never cast in the first place, or something like that.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure.
And it doesn't work automatically.
But if I have some time, I can undo the reincarnation spell!
That's...
Freaking awesome!
But...
I realize now...
These elves aren't bad guys.
Not at heart, anyway.
And the one that was controlling luck...
He's gone.
Does that mean that he died again?
He was...
Smiling at the end.
I sensed a kind person.
That was his true self.
I think it's good that you set him free.
This whole thing...
It's so sad.
And scary, too.
Got that right.
I promise.
For the sake of the elves and the humans,
I'll use this new sword to bring everyone back!
Yeah!
Wait, did you just say bring everyone back?
It's true.
A bunch of people are being controlled by elves.
They're on the offensive.
Huh?
Seriously?
This is a crisis.
Wait.
That's why all those flashes of light shot up into the sky.
There were a lot of them around the capital.
The giant rock thing was headed that way, too.
We have to go!
The Clover Kingdom needs protection!
Yes.
But before we do that, we'd better return to base
and regroup with the rest of the Black Bulls.
Yeah!
Don't worry, I can get us there in no time!
Huh?
My body remembers how the mana felt when that elf kid was with me!
I bet I can get even stronger!
Go ahead!
Cause that means I'm just gonna become that much stronger than you!
Good idea!
And if you want, I'd be happy to train you!
You cocky little brat!
Almost there!
What happened?
Everything's been trashed.
Don't tell me the elves got to it!
Ah!
Oh, hey!
Wait, who's been feeding all of you?
The captain's magical beasts.
I'm glad you're safe.
So where's everybody else?
Over there?
Hey!
You guys!
I'm so embarrassed!
You're in shock!
No wait, they're always like that!
Let me tell you...
Huh?
Who's that weirdo?
Listen!
I'm really gonna need you to try to use your words for once, okay?!
Ah!
I guess I'm Magna too?!
It's good to have you back safely.
Wow.
What happened to this place?
Well...
And you!
What's your story?
Wel-come back, Magna.
How do you know my name?
I think I'd remember meeting you, bed-head.
guitar sings
Don't get auto lost...
What the hell?!
The last of my mana's draining away!
Ow.
Your magic!
Magic...
impacted members of можете
Violet-
Soul sings
the place! In fact, he's been here longer than anyone. He's got some disease that wears down
people's magic power. Say hello to Henry! Henry? This guy's a great friend. He used to come visit
me all the time, and because I don't have any magic, his disease didn't affect me at all.
I'll tell you the truth, I kind of thought he was a ghost at first. I like Asta lots. He's my
friend. I missed him. This is so crazy. I really thought everybody knew about Henry from the
beginning. I probably should have said something, huh? I can't believe he's been creeping around
our base this whole time. Kind of makes you wonder if this place has any other secrets.
Hey, we still don't know what happened here. Oh no! Oh gosh, I didn't know! Could at least
one of you learn to talk! No way. Ghost 2? He's been possessed? I know this is serious,
but how did you get that? Yeah, I know, but remember, there's another person controlling
him. It's not like he attacked the base because he doesn't want to be friends anymore.
Leave it! Leave it! That's what I think too, Gray! The fact that he didn't kill you guys
then and there probably means that the real Ghost is still fighting for control.
After that...
Ghost headed for the royal capital? How do you understand any of this?
We have to bring Ghost to his senses, but I'm all out of magic power.
You two should rest up. Asta and I can take care of it.
Just hang in there a little longer, Ghost!
Whoa. Whatever that is, it's making the ground shake.
Oh no. The magic power is overwhelming.
Never forgive. Never forgive.
Charmy? It can't be.
Who did it?
Charmy's been turned into an elf.
Not her too.
I'm furious!
Who destroyed the vegetable garden that I was growing back there?
I want names!
Wait, nope. She's normal.
Oh, that's good.
Do you understand how much effort I put into that garden?
I fertilized it and watered it and gave it all my love and care.
I went out searching for yummy snacks to share with you guys and rushed straight home
even though I was starving. This is a thing I did!
I'm disgusted!
You mean that noise was your stomach?
Well, sauce isn't enough to satisfy my appetite!
It's so much sauce!
So are you three responsible for the Veggie Massacre?!
Uh, no. Of course not. That's cruel.
We would nab her.
Alright. Then, who was it?
Um, I think it was the Eye of the Midnight Sun and some elves.
Eye of the Midnight Sun and some elves?
Then come with me, everyone! We're gonna give those jerks a beating they won't forget!
Oh, believe me. I'd love to join you, but I'm fresh out of magic at the moment.
Yeah, I'm running pretty low, too, actually.
Huh? You mean you can't help avenge my garden?
Sorry.
That's not a problem!
Cut creation magic!
Safe cook! Catch him!
What?
Hurry! Get cooking!
Why, though?
We don't have time to stuff our faces right now!
We should get to the Capitol!
I don't know about this!
Eat!
I'm so confused.
Eat it!
Okay, I guess I am a little bit hungry.
Uh, thanks for the food!
Well?
This is delicious, Chari!
It's so delectable, I can't stand it!
Well, hey, what is that?
My magic's coming back!
That's right, the more you consume the Hatch Chef's cooking, the more your magic power increases.
There's that intense mana again!
You just saved the day, Charmy!
Yeah, you're amazing!
Now we can set up for the Capitol!
Keep eating!
I want everyone to clean their plants!
But go slow!
Savor the flavor!
Baby, after this, I'll finally have some magic power!
You can't multiply by zero!
But don't stop the Aiden!
And I'll just eat my feelings!
You should get in on this, Henry!
It's pretty yummy!
But I'll absorb everyone's magic!
Who cares?
We'll just keep scarfing it down!
Easy for you to say!
Some of us actually have magic, you know!
It's so good!
Clostrumbrill are elves now!
And that chubby blonde guy is too!
Oh no, the captain was going to their base!
I'm sure he can handle it!
Fenril's still injured!
Where's Noelle?
She and her crazy-haired brother are on their way to the Capitol!
We'd better catch up then!
Zora's with him!
Also, he's part of a squad now!
What?
That smart aleck is a black bull?
Apparently!
You haven't eaten enough, Gray!
Sorry!
I'm having so much fun, guys!
Right.
These are the black bulls I remember.
You're not done eating until I say so!
And being here with them is extra special.
What?
The hell is that?
It's so cool!
Still kind of scary, though!
Recombination magic.
The raging black bull.
Charging style.
I've never seen a magic smell like that!
Fuck about badass!
Climb aboard!
Let's go!
It's time to move out!
We're going to protect the Glover Kingdom from danger!
Because that's what the black bulls do!
Yeah!
Off to the Capitol!
Black bulls go!
探してる
Path of Revenge, Path of Atonement!
Yay! I'm ready for a challenge!